Jimmy Yuan

Education

Stony Brook University – Bachelor of Science: Information Systems,

Minor: Business, May 2016 Dean's List, G.P.A. – 3.57

Work Experience

MasterCard Worldwide, New York, NY

Web Developer – Customer Technical Communication July 2016 – Present

• I will optimize the workflow of the department by creating various websites and web applications.

Stony Brook University Faculty Student Association, Stony Brook, NY

Web Developer – Marketing

January 2015 – January 2016

- Optimize and apply UX principles to the FSA Website
- Create pages and customize CSS for certain pages
- Transfer and Update content to the site CMS (OmniUpdate)

MasterCard Worldwide, St. Louis, MO

Web Developer – Customer Technical Communication June 2014 – August 2015

- Created a ticketing system for the department
- Created a metrics dashboard which fed off the data in the ticketing system
- Automated workflow for the CTC Team
- Explored Information Security principles and procedures

Bloomberg LP, New York, NY

Installations Intern - Technical Operations

May 2013 - August 2013

- Interacted with customers to assist them in installing Bloomberg Professional and Anywhere Licenses, which also includes registering Biometric Devices
- Managed an order queue with ~40 orders per day
- Learned different areas of the Bloomberg business by shadowing Web Development, Technical Support, Software Quality Assurance, Information Systems, and Networking

Stony Brook University, Stony Brook, NY

Teachers Assistant – Computer Science Department February 2013 - May 2013

- Assisted Computer Science students with HTML/CSS/JavaScript/PHP
- Helped students troubleshoot technical issues
- Graded class work and proctored web design exams
- Substituted for professor and taught students when the professor was out

About Me



Hello, I am Jimmy Yuan a Web Developer in New York City. I major in Information Systems and minor in Business. I have worked throughout most of the school year at various jobs around the school. During the summer I've interned at companies such as Bloomberg LP and MasterCard Worldwide.

Contact Me

Email:

The Jimmy Yuan@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/thejimmyyuan

Skills

- Web Development HTML 5, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Python, Perl, and PHP
- Knowledge in Database Design
- JAVA Programming Language
- Experience with Drupal and OmniUpdate
- Experience in trouble shooting various Computer Hardware and Software Issues
- Proficient in Microsoft Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8. 10
- Proficient in Adobes Photoshop, Microsoft Office, and SharePoint
- Conversation Chinese(Mandarin and Cantonese)